Control when people can post to the
general ledger.
Hi.
In this video, we're going to show you
how you can take control of your month
and process or year and process in terms
of who can post to your general ledger
and when.
First of all, I want some settings to
apply for the entire company. And I can
set those up in the general ledger
setup.
So, let's just go there.
In general ledger setup, you'll see that
I've allowed posting with these two
fields, allow posting from and allow
posting to,
to happen in the month of November
through December. So, that's fine.
But, since we're now closing down
November, I don't want people to post in
November anymore. So, what I'm going to
do is I is I'm going to pull forward
this allow posting from until December
1st. Now,
by default, anyone in the company can
only post in December.
But, I still want to allow some people
to post in November. And this can then
be overwritten at the user setup page.
So, let's just go there.
What you can see here is that I still
allow Carlos to post in the month of
November with these settings in the
allow posting from and allow posting to
fields.
So, that's a great way to lock a posting
or a period down for a for the entire
company while opening up for a few
select people who are in this case, for
example, the accountants who wants to
close down the month.
So, with that, you can see how it's easy
to manipulate and take control over
these accounting periods and who can
post what and when.
Thank you for watching.